Right, right, right. So you have no idea.
- She must've dropped out.
- Exactly.
For real?
- You're kidding.
- So suddenly?
Oh, there she is.
Oh! There she is.
SHARAN (21)
LOUNGE HOSTESS
- Grandma Higa.
- Yes. Hello, welcome.
- Ms. Higa?
- Oh, she went to see Ms. Higa.
Thank you for coming to see me
all the way out here.
- I'm glad to see you.
- It's been a while.
Thank you, yeah. Uh-huh.
- It's chilly, are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm okay.
- Glad to hear it.
- Thank you for the other day.
Let's sit down and talk.
- How old are you right now?
- I'll be turning 22 real soon.
- Oh, you'll be 22?
- Twenty-two, yeah.
- I see.
- That's right.
I got married when I was 22.
- You did?
- We thought we were too young,
but figured it was the best thing to do,
because we both wanted to go to school.
So we decided we would do that
while starting our life together,
and finish it that way.
That's right.
- Okay, wow.
- Yeah.
- So, I want your advice on something.
- Mmm. Mmm.
So I have a one-sided crush, and I guess
I've been finding it really difficult,
- and I've just been crying every day.
- I see. Uh-huh.
I've been feeling like love is so painful,
especially one-sided.
- Aw.
- Yeah.
You know, it's best
to always be honest with yourself.
Just because you want
to be liked by that person,
you should never act in a way
that isn't true to yourself.
- Ah, yeah, yeah.
- Be honest and don't hold resentment.
- Okay? Don't do things like that.
- Yeah.
- Always be yourself.
- I get jealous.
- Of course you do.
- That's something
- I shouldn't be telling the other person.
- You shouldn't.
- But I did tell him. That I get jealous.
- Oh, yeah?
I got angry at him.
- You were angry?
- Because I like him, I got jealous.
- I see.
- I guess that's a bad trait of mine.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I know I have to fix it.
Mmm, that's right.
Just remember,
that's what will help you mature.
- Okay?
- Mmm.
So while I do understand how you feel,
remember, regardless of whether you end up
getting married to that person or not,
if you can treat them with kindness before
parting, then you've become an adult.
Mmm.
So, you ended up crying in front of him?
Um, yeah, I cried
in front of the person I like,
And also, this person I had a crush on,
has his own crush,
but it's not clear how she feels.
There are three guys after her.
It's Tai-chan. You know,
the one with tattoos on his face?
So, yeah, there are three guys,
including him, who like that girl.
- That so?
- She's popular.
- It's like that, huh?
- Yeah.
Wow, I see.
Well, try to be in good spirits.
- Mmm.
- Don't feel sorry for yourself.
You have your own life,
and you're still so young.
You can do anything you want to, right?
There are so many paths you can take,
so I want you to keep that in mind. Okay?
You can't let something like this
discourage you, okay?
Keep your chin up. All right?
- I'll try my best.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for your time.
- Of course.
Poor thing, you're really going through
a hard time right now, huh?
So, when you feel like crying,
let it all out.
But, even with that,
you have to walk your own path
Because when you do that,
a path will open for you.
You shouldn't do bad things
or act in spite.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Because you'll end up
hating that feeling just as much as this.
Keep your chin up.
I promise, if you live like that,
you'll definitely be given chances.
- Yeah?
- I'll try my best.
Hang in there, really. You're doing great.
- It's super painful.
- Chin up. I know it is.
But I'll try my best.
Oh, man. There's nothing we can do, huh?
- I guess not.
- Yeah.
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
Oh.
- Sorry.
- Oh, where were you?
- Welcome back.
- You scared us.
- Sorry about that.
- Jeez!
Where were you?
- What a relief.
- I'm really sorry. Seriously.
It's fine. We're glad you're still here.
- What happened?
- Well…
I went to see Grandma Higa.
- What?
- I had no idea.
- Oh, that's what happened?
- I went to see her to…
- To sort out your feelings?
- Yeah. To sort out my feelings.
Mmm.
So, yeah, we talked about it.
Um, yeah.
I need to gather my thoughts.
- No, take your time.
- It's totally fine.
- Give her the tissues.
- No, I'm not gonna cry.
I'm not crying anymore.
I promised Grandma Higa.
- Good for you.
- Yeah.
And what she told me was…
that if I don't grow as a person,
I won't be, you know,
given as many chances.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- That's what she said.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
She also said
that I had to be strong.
So, I'm really glad I got to talk to her.
- Mmm.
- That sounds good.
- And thank you all for cooking.
- No problem.
- Thanks.
Let's eat.
- Yeah.
- But I'm glad. Really.
- We're in this together.
- No one left out.
- True.
Yeah, because we should
all be graduating together.
KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIMER
Yeah, I realized I need to be strong.
- Yeah.
- All good.
- I'm sorry. Truly, to everyone.
- No, it's okay.
- Don't apologize.
- We're just glad you came back.
- Sorry.
- Let's try our best.
- I'll try my best.
- Let's go.
- I will.
- All right!
- I'm so glad Sharan came back.
- What a relief. Thank you, Ms. Higa.
- A grandmother's kindness.
- Such kindness, right?
She was saying you should never
act spitefully toward one another.
Even though it may sound obvious,
it's not something you can easily do.
But Sharan seemed
to really take it to heart,
- and I think she did a good job.
- Yeah.
Her face had changed when she came back.
The moment when people overcome something,
is the moment
when they shine the brightest.
That's so true.
And they're the coolest,
cutest, and most beautiful, so…
Mmm.
I mean, that makes us human.
- It's truly amazing.
- That's exactly what I thought as well.
I'd fall for Sharan if I were Tai-chan.
- Right?
- I'd be like, "Wait. She's cute!"
- True.
- Absolutely adorable.
I'm glad.
- All good.
- We're relieved.
Whoa!
- Let's go!
- Okay!
- Wow!
- Happy birthday!
Wow, those are amazing!
Happy birthday to you
Yes, there's more!
Happy birthday--
Sharan! Happy Birthday!
- And also…
- Rinrin and Kahochi's
- Coming of Age celebration!
- Ah, thank you so much.
Okay, the three of you, blow out
your candles. All three of you, come on.
- Come over here and blow them out.
- Wait, these are so cute.
- Incredible.
- Insane!
- Aren't these well-made?
- These are homemade?
That's genius! Right…
- All right.
- Ready…
Set… go!
- You can do it!
- Let's go, Sharan!
Wow, what great smiles! Look at them!
Congratulations!
- Good for you!
- Congratulations!
RINRIN, KAHOCHI 20
SHARAN
- These are super cute.
- I'm impressed.
A birthday and a Coming of Age.
It's above and beyond.
- Right?
- Beautifully made, right?
- Well, then, let's all dig in!
- Let's eat!
- Let's eat.
- Here we go.
- Tasty!
- Mmm, so good!
- Now this is a cake.
- Delicious.
- Tasty.
- Super good.
- Yum!
- Seriously?
Tastes like proper cake.
MARU (28)
HOST/PRESIDENT
I'm so happy.
- Mmm!
- Thank you.
- This is a good day.
- Have a piece.
- We turned it around.
- We did. Are you happy?
Yeah, 'cause of all the compliments.
- I get that.
- I'm so happy.
Right, but it's not like
we're celebrating you, Maru.
I'm sorry? Hey, watch it!
Just like in The Manzai, remember?
Oh, man, this is fun.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KAZUMA
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
MARU
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
AYACHERU
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
RINRIN
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
RYOPI
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
SARA
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
KITASHINCHI'S NO.1 HOSTESS
BLEEDING BIG-SIS ENERGY
MIMI
STRAIGHT-SHOOTING FORMER MMA CHAMP
KAMAKEN
POPULAR OKINAWAN HOSTESS LOOKING FOR LOVE
KAHOCHI
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
- Oops.
- Oh?
- What is it?
- Here it comes.
It's the evening sauna time.
Oh.
The one who can go in the sauna today is
someone who hasn't been
in with a woman yet.
Oh.
- It's Kazuma.
- Oh.
- What?
- Oh, it's me…
- Why him?
- What?
- Great.
- Good.
- It's finally me, at last.
- You've wanted this.
It's now time to choose the woman
you'd like to go to the sauna with.
- Kahochi's watching.
- Go on, Kazuma.
I choose Sara.
Yes. Finally!
That was a super-quick decision.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Right. We ate cake,
so our faces will be puffy tomorrow.
Thank you for the cake.
- Hey. You better tell her how you feel.
- Have a good time.
Don't touch me.
- Ah, nice one, Ryopi.
- Youthful rivals in love.
REFRESHED
- He's so scary.
- What a picture.
He's terrifying.
This is my first time.
I did it with the guys,
but never with a girl.
Insane, huh?
This is a terrifying couple. Look at them.
Sara is striking in her own right
with her traditional Japanese tattoos.
Today was another eventful day, wasn't it?
- A lot happened, yeah.
- Right?
Yeah, so much happened.
What'd you think of it all?
- About what? The Ryopi thing?
- Uh, yeah, exactly.
Well, it's not really about how I felt,
but I guess I felt like I'd lost to him.
Oh. Well, personally,
it was just surprising to me.
- Oh, you mean Ryopi going after you now?
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, Ryopi seemed like
he was pretty serious about it.
- Seriously?
- Yeah. I guess we'll see at graduation.
And my feelings
won't change before then, so…
The thing is, even if Ryopi and I
both have feelings for you,
- it's ultimately up to you to decide.
- Mmm.
So, the only thing I have left to do
is to go full steam ahead.
- That's really something.
- Yeah.
- And tell you how I feel about you.
- That's really something.
- Is it really?
- It is. Really, it is.
Show me your back tattoo.
- What is this?
- Stand up like this.
Stand up? No way!
- What, are you embarrassed?
- Yeah.
Well, this is tattoo communication.
This here is…
- This green part--
- Whoa, that's amazing!
I could just stare at it forever.
- Is that what you think?
- Ah, I'm enjoying this.
Man… Wow, it's so tasteful.
- Whoa.
- "Whoa."
Can I take a look?
Up there, it looks really nice.
Sharan? Come on, let's talk.
You doing good?
I'd say I'm doing better than before.
- Don't cry.
- I'm not gonna cry.
- Ah.
- I'm stronger now.
Oh, okay.
I've decided not to cry anymore.
Like… How do I put this?
I fall apart when I like someone too much.
So I'm trying hard
to not think about it too much.
Mmm.
I'm going to try to not get angry,
or get jealous anymore either, yeah.
So that's what I'm feeling.
I know there isn't much time left.
Hmm.
Hmm, yeah.
Hey.
I'll try my best.
Hmm, the thing is,
I have to grow as a person.
I tried to forget about my feelings
for him, but I still like him,
and I really want to date him, so…
She really likes him, doesn't she?
I'm going to try my best.
And also, I want to show everyone
how much I've grown.
I'm determined to change. Mmm-hmm.
Tai-chan should be noticing this, right?
No, but the way Tai-chan
was looking at her…
- It was different. Yeah.
- Different, right?
Like, "Oh, she's cute."
- That's always the story with this guy.
- It is.
- This expression…
- Right?
- Constantly making this face.
- Yes, exactly. That's true.
When it comes to Tai-chan,
I don't want him to waver anymore. Right?
Not at this stage. That's a good point.
But, I mean…
he's unsure.
- What's this mist for?
- Good morning!
- Hey, guys.
- Here they are.
- Good morning.
- Hey, how are you?
- Kaho's the best at it.
- Morning.
- I forgot my tumbler.
Are we ready?
Shh. Here it comes.
- What will it be today?
- Good morning!
Today, you are all
going to be helping out the locals.
- The day has finally come.
- Yeah.
However, because you also need
to work on the bench,
- you will be splitting into two groups.
- We're splitting up.
RUNE (28)
RAPPER/BUSINESS OWNER
The bench-making team is Rune, Ryopi,
Sara, and Rinrin.
Everyone else, please go
and help out in the local community.
- Well then, here we go. Let's get it!
- Go!
- Yay.
- This guy.
I'm the only one
who looks like an auto mechanic.
An auto mechanic? We all do.
- Let's do this.
- Paint's dry.
We're gonna finish this today.
Oh, hey,
what colors should we use on this?
Well, I've bought pink
and light blue already.
Oh, okay.
I think those are
the colors of this school.
Mmm, right.
It's pretty peaceful, isn't it?
Yeah.
I wish there were no more wars.
Friendship!
- Good morning.
- Hello there!
Good morning, sir.
- Been a while.
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
- I flunked.
- Oh!
- Ahh! It's Mr. Hentona!
- Just you, huh?
- I can't believe it!
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you for having us.
- Hello.
- Thanks.
I'm Kazuma. I'm from Kanagawa.
- Right.
- I'm Kaho. I'm from Urasoe.
What? So am I!
- From Urasoe?
- Makiminato.
How should we do this today?
Let's work in groups.
Four of you work over here,
the others there.
- Mmm.
- All right.
Those of you over here,
I want you to paint.
- What's this shed for?
- This is for a fruit stand.
And also, I'll be making snacks.
Shakes and stuff.
Oh, wow.
I want to make it
into a shop where I can sell smoothies.
- Sounds good.
- Nice.
Let's paint it nice and pretty.
- Hey, Mister.
- What's up?
I don't think I got your name.
- I'm Mr. Hentona.
- Come again?
- Hentona.
- Hentona?
- I'll go with Mr. Tona then.
- Call me Ma-chan.
Ma-chan?
- It's well-known I'm Ma-chan.
- Oh, we'll go with Ma-chan.
Am I looking good up here?
Yes, you look cool.
MIMI (29)
HOSTESS
Have you gotten used to life here?
- Pretty used to it.
- How many days?
- What's with the questions?
- Well, I don't know.
Well, I've never really chatted
with you, Kamaken.
I haven't had
a lot of chances to talk to you.
- We haven't seen much of each other.
- That's right.
- That's been our story, hasn't it?
- The thing is, you're super popular.
- So I thought it must be intense for you.
- No, no.
Yeah, so, to be honest,
I decided to back off.
- I see.
- Yeah.
I think when it comes to you,
I think I want to be good friends
with you, I really do.
Huh?
Interesting move.
- Why would he say that?
- I know, right?
I'm so glad. Because you all came,
I think we might actually finish
all of the painting.
- Great.
- Let's finish it.
This is fun, the sun feels so nice.
- Sunlight's amazing, right?
- Yeah.
Go for it, princess.
Go on.
You got this, girl.
Stop, you're making me feel
like a hostess.
She can say things like that
when she's with Tai-chan.
- Tai-chan keeps getting in my way, dude.
- No, I'm not.
Now I'm sad.
Doing great, Tai-chan!
Seriously, can I--
Can I beat him to death or something?
- Auntie gets angry so easily.
- The heck are you talking about?
Oh man.
I feel happy.
Take that.
Okay, let me put this in.
- It's rigid.
- Then we use this.
You see, this is called a windbreak.
You know those tea trees
that grow like this?
Well, I dug about 70 holes for them.
Wow.
I want you to insert
and plant them in the holes.
Mmm.
They'll act as a windbreak
to protect the bananas.
This really has been a great experience.
I never do stuff like this
in my daily life.
AYACHERU (24)
HOSTESS
- Everything going well?
- Yep, all good.
That's what I like to hear.
- I'm so glad I came here.
- Seriously.
- Come back again.
- Sure. I'll come visit.
We're done.
If you stretch too far
when doing it, you'll most likely fall.
- If I stretch out my arm?
- Be careful.
Make sure you move the stepladder
when you get to that part.
Okay, got it.
- Make sure to do that, okay?
- Uh-huh.
- Wow, it's streaking.
- How long were you in Tokyo?
Until 2021.
After graduating from high school here,
I moved to Tokyo,
and I lived there for 40 years.
- Which high school?
- Naha Technical.
- Mmm.
- I was part-time.
A delinquent, you mean.
I think Kahochi
is gonna confess to Ma-chan.
- No way.
- Look.
- Wait, are you two talking trash?
- Not at all. I didn't mean to.
You think I'm a funny old man.
No. I was just saying
that Kahochi's seems interested in you.
Oh, okay.
I'm gonna start cleaning up.
Almost done.
Do you notice
when people are looking at your boobs?
You guys are seriously
out of your minds. Can you cut it out?
- I'm dying!
- I can't not do it.
I just can't help but look at 'em.
Seriously, because it's you saying it,
I somehow don't find it gross. You know?
- Dor real?
- I somehow don't.
It's totally fine. Wait, but not--
Oh, yeah. I gotta stop staring
at your boobs.
How's it going, Kahochi?
Are you settling in yet?
- Oh, I'm totally settled in, but…
- Mmm.
- Is there anyone you like?
- There is.
- Who?
- Kazuma.
- Wait, really?
- Yeah.
- Then you gotta go for it!
- That's why I tried to go over there.
- I think it's fine to switch up teams.
- No, it's totally fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- You're so mature.
- I sure am.
- How are you? Getting along?
- Let's go have a smoke together, Ma-chan.
- Wanna have a smoke?
- Yeah.
Mr. Hentona is so kind.
Island bananas are super tiny.
Hey, what are these? Papayas?
- Papayas. Mmm.
- I see.
- So you grow papayas too?
- Yeah, exactly.
All right. Let's take a seat here.
- Okay.
- Here we are. Great smoke spot.
- I got one for you.
- Thanks.
- Okay. here we are.
- Got something to ask the old guy?
- What I want to ask the old guy is…
Well, so everyone's here
to find love, right?
- Mmm.
- But…
I'm going to tell you,
because it's just you and me right now,
- but I've already failed at love twice.
- Oh. You have?
Oh, but you know, I have a kid too.
So this is my kid's name, Rua.
- Oh, is that so? Oh.
- Yeah.
- So you're a single mom.
- That's right.
- I am interested in someone.
- Hmm.
But that person is already
head-over-heels for another girl.
- Oh.
- I won't let that stop me, though.
- Mmm, mmm.
- Once I'm in love, I mean.
I'm just interested right now,
so I don't really know what to do.
- Don't be afraid to fail.
- Right? That's true.
- Even if you get rejected, go for it.
- Yeah, I'm perfectly okay with that.
- We have that Okinawan positivity.
- Right? We don't let things get to us.
In this world, there are so many you won't
get to meet during your lifetime.
- I agree.
- So many you'll never meet.
So, the fact that you were able
to meet is already fate, in a way.
- At the very least, you'll be friends.
- Good point.
It's that way with everything,
including love.
Sometimes, people might suddenly
feel that rush and fall in love,
but there are others who take their time.
- That's true, yeah.
- Some people discover qualities they like.
- Right? Right?
- Mmm-hmm.
And then they develop feelings.
It all depends on the person.
So there's no need to rush, but if you're
interested in him basically, well,
he doesn't have to be your boyfriend.
I think it's okay to start off just
as friends in the beginning, you know?
- Mmm.
- It's not like making a brave attempt is…
It isn't pathetic, not at all.
It's not pathetic.
- Not taking a chance is more embarrassing.
- Yeah, that's right.
You bet.
- That's right. It's all good.
- Yeah.
I got it.
Do a good job raising
your little one, okay?
- Yeah.
- All right then.
I'll raise her with care. I have to find
someone who cherishes her like I do.
Yes, you will. You will.
But if they fall in love with you,
I'm sure they'll fall in love
with your kid automatically.
So I don't think
you have to worry about that. I wouldn't.
- Good luck.
- Yeah, I'll try my best. Thanks.
- Thanks, Grandpa.
- Good luck.
Thanks, Ma-chan.
- It's done.
- It's so cute.
- It really is.
- The yellow is so nice!
- It's super cute.
- Well, thank you all for your hard work.
Thank you so much.
Take care. We'll come again.
- Thank you.
- Please come back.
- We'll be back.
- I'll be waiting for you all.
- Thank you.
- See you again.
- Thanks, Ma-chan.
- Bye, take care.
BADLY IN LOVE
MARINE ACADEMY
- Seems like they're back.
- Here they are.
Welcome back.
- We finished the bench.
- Seriously? Where is it?
We put your hopes
into this bench, Kamaken.
- Welcome back.
- We're back.
- What was that, huh?
- They're all buddies now.
- Yeah, even Tai-chan.
- It's in the classroom, let's go see it.
- Yeah, we want you all to come with us.
- Shall we open the door?
- Shall!
- I shall!
- Come in!
- Whoa!
- Wow, amazing!
- Wow, so cute!
- Isn't it amazing? Really good.
- Amazing!
- It's adorable!
- This makes me happy.
- Nice!
- Like it?
- This is amazing!
- Such a great job.
- We did it under the blazing sun.
- You did good.
- Looks nice.
- This is dope. So pretty.
- I like the pink.
A gentle color.
- Colors are good.
- They'll definitely be happy.
The light blue is pretty.
Because you all worked hard
helping out the local community today,
alcohol will be allowed at dinner.
- Hell yeah!
- Toss me to celebrate.
Ready? And…
Hurray! Hurray!
However, overdrinking is prohibited.
"Overdrinking is prohibited."
Hey.
Yo.
- I'm so tired.
- Huh?
- Aren't you tired?
- No, I'm not tired.
So…
Yeah, so, I wanted some time
with you today, because…
- I want to say something.
- What is it?
It's not something I want to say,
but something I have to tell you.
And that's… I don't know, it's really…
something I can only tell someone
who's special to me.
Yeah.
When I was 19 years old…
Mmm-hmm.
- I got married.
- Okay.
- I'm 30 now, but…
- Mmm.
I got married when I was 19 or 20,
and we had a kid together.
And, well, we broke up, and…
Well, I haven't seen them
in about four years now.
- What?
- And that's because…
Um…
I was thinking about them,
or rather, I was thinking about my kid.
- They have a new dad, you know?
- Mmm-hmm.
I took that into consideration…
and decided not to see
my kid anymore. Yeah.
And that's what
I wanted to tell you today.
Hmm.
- Yeah.
- I think that's fine.
- "I think that's fine"?
- I think it's fine.
- It's fine?
- Well, I don't really…
- think anything of it.
- Hmm.
If you want to see them,
you should see them.
Mmm.
I don't think there's
anything wrong about it.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Is it something that burdens you?
Something like a weight?
No, but I didn't
want to tell it to just anyone.
- That's what you mean?
- Yeah.
Okay, how do I put this?
If hearing that made me leave,
then I can't help but think
our relationship was never that strong.
How do I put this…
I don't want to be weak, either.
Oh…
Well, you did say you always
put up a brave front.
- Like with… with a lot of things.
- I do.
- Mmm.
- I guess I don't show my weaknesses.
Ah, you don't like to show them?
Well, mm…
With my first relationship,
I would cry in secret and stuff.
Oh…
- Your first?
- Yeah, because he was physically abusive.
- Oh.
- So I cried in secret and stuff.
Oh, you did?
But I seriously can't imagine how a guy
could abuse his partner in any way.
Mmm, there was
a lot of stuff that happened.
Like, he strangled me and pushed me over.
That kind of stuff…
- Oh…
- Yeah.
But, you know, I'm happy that you told me.
What?
Huh? No, it's nothing.
Her smile is so cute.
She's letting out a smile. It's so cute.
Well, I was surprised.
It turns out that Kamaken…
had more weighing on his mind
than I thought he did.
Like, with my dad currently…
back in high school,
that's when he and I actually,
we stopped seeing each other.
So, like…
because, well, I'm experiencing it
as the child in the situation,
I feel like
not being able to see each other
is…
really painful. Yeah, that's what I think.
- That was nice.
- Yeah.
So this means that
Rinrin and Kamaken are solid.
- But, didn't he say something to Mimi too?
- He certainly did.
- Ah!
- Kamaken, I mean.
Wait, that's right.
"Everyone was going for you,
so I gave up."
- Like he withdrew.
- That was a little concerning, right?
It's like, "Don't say that!" You know?
- She was waiting for you.
- You were waiting for me?
- So cute.
- Enough.
- I'll get some.
- Defrost that.
Leave it out of Rinrin's.
So we'll wrap them
in gyoza wrappers, right?
- Yeah, we're doing a whole bunch.
- Go cook with Mimi.
There's a lot of stuff
I'll need your help with later on.
- Here.
- Hey. You wanna smoke?
Yeah, sure.
I've also been
to Chidori Park in Kanagawa.
Chidori Park?
Isn't that near Minato Mirai?
This'll take 15 minutes, don't open it.
You can really taste it.
- Fifteen-minute break.
- Use it if you want.
You know, I've been thinking
about it ever since I came here…
Hmm.
…and I think I'm probably
not the type of guy
who wants to go out
and try to win someone's heart.
I see.
- I think, "This is too much trouble."
- I get that, man.
I mean, it's like, whatever.
I'm just not sure it's worth all of this.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, I mean, honestly, Kamaken…
I found myself not really caring
about pursuing it anymore.
- Are you serious?
- For real.
No way.
- Isn't the situation changing?
- I'm being serious.
- Really?
- Yeah, and…
- I found myself thinking that.
- Have you talked to Mimi today?
Like at any point?
Because I haven't seen you two talking.
Well, you know, we haven't
really talked about anything--
- Let's do the thing.
- Oh, yes.
- Ayacheru, can you finish this?
- Sure.
- Sorry. Thank you.
- Okay.
What? What's wrong?
So it was a big deal
that she went to Tai-chan.
It's normal.
- Why are you so loud today?
- Let's eat!
Cheers!
- Thank you. Let's eat.
- Cheers!
- Welcome back.
- Good job.
- Let's get it going!
- Cheers.
- Sara, good job.
- Wow, this is yummy.
- Lots of alcohol.
- You haven't eaten anything.
- I'm drinking a lot. Seriously.
Doesn't that make it harder?
To eat I mean?
- Taste so good.
- I don't know.
Hmm, tastes like it.
I don't want this one.
SMOKERS' LOUNGE
Wow, Kazuma, you're in a harem.
Surrounded by two beautiful women
with tattoos.
This is a good time.
It is. We have to cherish it.
It's a precious, irreplaceable time.
I would also like to take a tour
of the guys' room.
- You wanna come?
- You should go.
- The guys' room?
- Yeah.
Isn't the girls' room super fancy?
- It is big.
- Yeah, the girls' room is so big.
Wow, nice. Hello.
- Hey…
- Come in, come in.
- Don't be shy.
- This room has a manly vibe.
Smells better than the girls' room.
Oh, and everyone said that you're good
at drawing. I wanna see it too.
This one is a traditional style,
Japanese traditional tattoo.
- These are like study pieces.
- Mm-hmm. This is cool.
Wow. What is this bonji?
- This is my Chinese zodiac sign.
- Oh, in which year were you born?
- The year of the rabbit.
- Oh, rabbit. Cute.
I was going to draw
Sara's Chinese zodiac sign too.
- Which year?
- Hers is the same as mine.
- Rabbit? You two are the same age?
- Rabbit. Yeah, exactly.
Wow.
This is really nice. I've thought about
becoming a tattoo artist too.
- You did say you wanted to try being one.
- Yeah, I did.
These are amazing.
They're so nice.
Do you draw here
when you have free time? Making a new one?
Yeah. I'm working on the drawing
- I'm going to give Sara.
- I see.
Should we talk?
- Yeah 'cause earlier…
- Yeah.
I was spending time with you today,
and you said that you wanted
to talk to me, so I thought--
Yeah, let's talk.
- Yeah.
- So, um--
It kind of makes me think,
because you have a thing with Rinrin.
Yeah.
We don't have many days left,
and there are people thinking about me.
- Yeah.
- And they're telling me their feelings.
I wouldn't want to reach the end
without talking to you, too.
Especially since, well I was thinking
about this while working today…
- And, well, you know I thought that…
- Yeah.
Because of our age,
I felt like you'd understand me.
That's a good point.
You know, back when
I was going to fight Kazuma,
and you were the one to stop that fight…
I don't know, I've been interested in you.
I'm 29 years old,
and I've experienced a lot in this life.
Hmm.
Considering all of that,
I honestly thought at the time,
"You know, I really like Kamaken."
Wait, really?
- That's what I thought.
- When?
Wow, I didn't expect this.
But you must have had some kind of idea.
Because when we were hanging out
and smoking behind the gym,
you told me how you felt.
Well, that's true.
I thought, "Why do I have to lose
to a 20-year-old?"
I had absolutely no idea.
You're being pursued by three guys. Right?
And, you know,
Maru, Tai-chan, and Rune,
they are all pursuing you.
And I said I would back off.
I told everyone I would, and I did.
- Yeah.
- Don't back off. This is Badly In Love.
I came here to see
what you're made of, seriously.
You have a point.
I'm sorry, but I want to be clear.
There are three guys pursuing you.
Do you think you've narrowed it down
to one person yet?
I haven't decided yet.
Oh, I see.
- You really haven't?
- There's something missing,
in each of them.
- I'm going to get a drink. Excuse me.
- You're going back?
I don't know, I mean…
Well, there are a lot of guys
who want to talk to you.
Oh, so I have your permission?
- No, wait. That's not what I meant.
- Can I go? I'm asking you.
So tell me, is it okay if I go?
Kamaken.
I'm a little scared now.
- This girl's too strong.
- I can go, right?
Oh, what should I do?
This is hard. What do I do?
- What?
- Kamaken!
What's going on?
What is this?
Oh, this is so hard.
I don't know what to do?
Ryopi, can I talk to you for a second?
Oh, sure, no problem.
I'm really at a crossroads
right now, seriously.
I can imagine.
- In the end, I think it's all up to you.
- I wasn't thinking about it at all today.
- Oh.
- I wasn't thinking about talking to Mimi.
I was just being myself and trying
to have fun. That's how I behaved.
I think that was good.
I think she got that.
That's why Mimi wanted
to talk to you today, right?
I mean, she's probably thinking
about you too.
- Seriously, I just don't know what to do.
- I feel you.
I am at a major crossroads right now.
But, you know,
Rinrin is the kind of girl that--
It's going to be terrible
if she finds out.
I mean, there are six guys
at the school with me right now.
But to be honest, there's actually no one
I want to pursue for myself.
And really, I think
it's because of my trauma.
That's what I'd have to say.
I just honestly have
a hard time trusting men.
Um…
It all started
the first time I'd ever been cheated on.
I was a student.
And, well…
Yeah, at that time…
Um…
Well, you see, I was…
pregnant with his child.
But I remember thinking
I was still just a student.
We were still kids,
and we were going to have a kid.
We couldn't imagine that,
so we talked it over.
And, in the end, we made the decision
to give up the baby, but,
he cheated on me during that time,
which made me…
well…
So, from that point on,
more than other girls,
I started to think of men as…
You know…
I was checking each man thoroughly to see
if he was the one who wouldn't cheat,
lie, or go to other girls.
I came here to find love,
but I'm not very good at it.
And recently, it felt like…
Yeah, it's something I really worry about
so much, I can't sleep. It's on my mind.
I worry about it, even at work.
Yeah, so…
That's it. Hmm.
I can't figure it out.
It's like she's dealing with
the men as if she's at work.
- I think so.
- That's what I'm getting from this.
Also,
I'm sensing she
might not know how to love.
- How she behaves with Kamaken you mean?
- Yeah.
- When she asked, "Can I go?"
Judging from that behavior,
I think she's struggling with herself.
- Mmm.
- That's what I think.
She was obviously hurt
very deeply in her life.
- So, you can tell she's serious.
- I know.
You know, she didn't come
to Badly In Love just to mess around.
- She was the hardest to read.
- Yeah.
- Let's talk.
- Wait, what is he doing?
- Oh!
Scary.
Okay, so…
I don't know if Mimi was drunk or not,
but she told me, like,
"Come after me more."
Like, "Are you fine
with how it is right now?"
- That's what she said.
- Mmm… And?
But I wanted to bring you here
to tell you what we talked about.
And… Yeah. Mmm.
And It's true that I did want
to talk to her a little more.
Mmm-hmm.
But…
you were the one who made
those feelings go away.
But, I…
I didn't know she had that feeling.
Mimi wanted me to--
She was actually interested in me.
I thought she had no interest
in me. Really.
So, I don't know if that's really
how she is feeling or not.
Hmm. Then you should talk about it.
Hmm.
It's up to you.
I don't really care what you decide.
- I get that.
- Yeah.
It's up to you.
- Up to me?
- Yeah.
Anyway, until you make up your mind,
don't do anything to me, okay?
- I shouldn't.
- Yeah.
That's so cool! You're so cool, Rinrin!
She's so cool.
Are we done here?
Well, it would've been better
if I could've just said,
"No, I'm into Rinrin," when she said that.
But I couldn't say it.
How do I put it?
My heart is in so much turmoil.
I just don't know what I should do.
Good morning.
Yeah, well,
let's put aside the romance stuff.
- Mmm-hmm.
- But I'm rooting for you.
She has such a big heart.
Mmm.
Good luck.
- I'm rooting for you from afar.
- From afar?
- She's so cool.
- You don't have to do it from the shadows.
To tell you straight, I was actually
thinking of confessing my love to you.
Mmm.
Well, I know you've been
saying that from the start.
And it's true that I was happy
about that when I heard it.
Mmm-hmm.
- I'm very thankful to you.
- Her eyes have changed.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Yes.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
I'm not doing anything.
- I'm so grateful.
- For what?
- I'm grateful that you're here.
- Oh, are you? I see.
So, yesterday, you talked to Kamaken,
and you said you were interested in him.
I feel like the number of people
is increasing day by day.
- Mmm.
- You haven't smiled at me once.
Not since we were cooking yesterday.
I want to come at you straight
and be completely honest with you.
I want us both
to face each other honestly.
But I need you to face me too.
Otherwise, you know, I honestly wonder
if it's worth me trying to face you.
Because I'm thinking seriously.
- I understand.
- Yeah.
- You're so right.
- Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
- I wonder. He likes her so much…
- Yeah.
- Why doesn't he act a little more excited?
- I know.
- Rune is a little stiff and intimidating.
- Yeah.
No, it's more like,
he comes across as a little critical.
- It might be working against him.
- Hmm.
And Ayacheru,
she's still set on Maru, right?
She's like, "I'm rooting for you."
But what do you think
about how she feels, sensei?
I think that by acting all big-hearted,
she's trying to secure
a fallback place for Maru.
Mmm.
- So he can come back.
- Oh.
And she's trying to make sure he knows
that place will always be there for him.
- Mmm.
- That's what she's saying, right?
Hmm.
- She still likes him, right?
- I think she still likes him.
Hmm.
The graduation ceremony
is finally the day after tomorrow.
And tomorrow,
is the appreciation party for the locals.
MARU - AYACHERU
Let's start the final preparation.
I fell asleep.
- I like that.
- This is nice. Really nice.
- Yeah, it's starting to look good.
- I'm hot.
- Hey, that's nice.
- "It's free!"
Is it done?
- "It's free" is a nice touch.
It's like, "Welcome in!"
Isn't there an extra line
in the "free" character?
I made a mistake.
MASSAGE BOOTH
FREE!
- It's a prank.
- There are five lines. A prank?
FOOD
- Kahochi has a fever.
- She does?
- She does, it's pretty bad.
- Kaho, take care.
Aw.
- Wait, you have a fever?
- I do. It's 37.8.
- Oh, no.
- That's bad.
Poor Kahochi.
She must've caught a cold.
- What bad timing.
- Yeah.
Oh, poor Kahochi.
- Poor Kahochi.
- Is it bad?
It's 37.8.
- It is.
- Really?
It's not simmered down yet.
- She's still sick.
- Is that it?
And, this…
- Oh, Kazuma…
- Oh, Kazuma.
He's moving. He's making a move.
I'm gonna cut it. What is this?
I found it there. Let's use that.
- Wow, that'll make her happy.
- I'm coming in.
- He's so kind.
- Kahochi?
- Yeah?
- Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
- Is it okay if I come up?
- Yeah.
- The top?
- Kazuma, nice move.
Oh, you look like you're feeling bad.
I didn't know it was you.
What's this?
These are samples
of what we're going to serve tomorrow.
It's jello. You're not feeling well, yeah?
Right. This is great.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
There are four more of these,
so eat them whenever you want.
Yeah, wow, thank you.
- We all gotta make it to graduation.
- Yeah. You're so kind, Kazuma.
So, I'd like to talk,
I'd like to be with you, but…
- You might catch it too.
- Right. Take care of yourself.
Yeah, thanks.
Yeah, I hope you get better
before the graduation ceremony.
- Yeah.
- I'll do my best to get better.
- Yeah, well, take care.
Yeah, thank you.
- Good night. Take care of yourself.
- Good night, thank you.
- Yeah, get some rest.
- Okay.
- Bye-bye.
One day until the graduation ceremony.
Today, we have invited people from
the local area for the appreciation party.
Let's make the final preparations.
- It's sad.
- Yeah.
- The T-shirts are finally done!
- Yay!
- These are your T-shirts.
- Awesome!
So, let me unveil it.
- Whoa, let's see it.
- Ta-da!
- Great.
- Whoa, it's so cute!
- I look dope.
- It's cute.
It's amazing!
- Sara is sick!
- Looks like it's Sara's team.
We're a biker gang! Badly in Love.
All right, let's get ready.
- Everyone together, let's get it!
- Here we go.
Let's go.
- I think it's good.
- Thanks.
Let's do it from the edge.
- Kimcheese…
- Yeah, kimcheese is delicious, isn't it?
Can I add some meat too?
She still looks angry.
Oh no.
Let's welcome them.
- Yes.
- Open the door!
- Welcome.
- Yay!
Welcome!
- Hello!
- Hello.
Hi, welcome. Welcome.
- All right. Thank you.
- Hi, Grandma Higa.
- Grandma Higa.
- Oh, it's Ma-chan.
- No problem. It's Ryopi. Thanks a lot.
- Hello, everyone. Good to see you.
All right, everyone, please put this on
and let's have fun together.
Mmm-hmm.
- Oh, it looks great on you. It's the best!
- Oh, it's so cute.
Altogether, everyone.
Kwacchiisabira!
"Kwacchiisabira."
It means, "Thank you for the meal."
Ah, I see.
Is it good?
- Very good.
- Glad to hear that.
This is tasty.
The food is all really good.
- Oh, you think so?
- Yes, all the dishes are authentic.
- You went to see her, right?
- Yeah I did.
Yes, she came over.
- So you two are close.
- Oh, yes, we are.
- Since the day before yesterday.
- So, that's when.
- That's right.
- That's not fair.
Let me go next time.
I'll go for your advice too.
Let's do the ring toss, everyone.
- Go. Oh no!
- Oh wow.
Go!
They're having so much fun.
- That's nice.
- That is nice for them.
That's terrible.
- Don't be greedy.
- Don't be greedy!
- Take things one at a time in life.
- That's right.
- If you get greedy like this--
- Ryopi, she says, "One at a time in life."
- And, "Don't be greedy."
- Wow, that's so deep.
Madame Higa. Madame Higa…
- Good morning.
- Hey!
- Hi, everybody.
- Hey, Kaho!
- How are you?
- Feeling alive again?
- Yeah, all better now.
- Welcome back.
- Let's go.
- Did your fever go down?
My fever went down.
- I'm glad you could come back.
- Hmm?
- I'm so glad you came.
- Yeah, I'm glad.
You know, usually,
I don't have anyone taking care of me
when I'm sick, so I was really happy.
I was thrilled. My heart was pounding.
I was really happy.
I want to get my nails done.
- Nail art. Sara!
- Who's up for doing nails?
- I've never done it before.
- It'll be my first time ever.
- Is it pretty?
- It is.
- I'm glad.
- I've never done this.
- Looking good.
- Oh, it's pretty.
Looks great. They're having a blast.
- You gotta do this more.
- I love this color.
- Really? I'm glad.
- First time for everything.
Wow.
- The pink is so cute.
- I'm so happy.
- Thanks.
- Are you going to cut hair?
Let's go.
- See you later.
- Don't you want me to come see?
Yeah, you've definitely gotta come.
- Here? Like this?
- Yes, right there.
It feels good.
How many centimeters would you like
to cut? Two or three centimeters?
Which part?
- The back.
- The back?
Raise the neckline a little.
I'd like to have it shorter.
Sure.
Have you ever cut your father's hair?
- My father?
- Yes.
Well, my father…
We don't get along.
- Oh, you don't?
- Yes.
- Why?
- I used to play baseball.
- A lot of things happened.
- Mmm.
- And I quit playing baseball.
- Ah…
And we had been working together
as a team since I was little.
Oh, I see.
My father couldn't accept the fact that
I didn't want to play baseball anymore.
I see.
And he didn't know that I was
doing all kinds of crazy things outside.
That was your father's dream.
He wanted you to play baseball.
Yeah, that's right.
For your father's sake, and for yours…
Uh-huh.
I hope the day will come
when you can cut his hair.
- Yeah, I hope so.
- So do I.
Lately, I have been thinking
about how I can make up with him.
For now, you'll just keep doing
what you're doing.
Just keep doing your best
as long as you can.
You're right.
If you keep showing him that you're doing
your best, he'll understand someday.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Mmm-hmm.
Just a little more hair spray,
and Ma-kun will be ready
- to take a job as a host.
- A host?
- No way! Really?
- Became a host?
- He will become a host.
- No way.
- Here he is!
- Hello.
- The number one host.
- What do you think?
The number one host!
Whoa!
Oh, you look so cool!
Make the pose, like "ta-da!"
Oh, he looks so cool!
- Tai-chan is really skilled.
- Tai-chan is amazing!
Everyone, look at this.
- Wow!
- This is for you.
We made a bench.
- All of us together.
- Wow!
So, we all got to visit
Grandma Higa's amazing place.
It was a place that has a great view,
so we all wanted to put a bench there.
- Oh, thank you!
- Something to remember us by.
And we all wrote our names on it.
So, once Ms. Higa and everyone else
signs it, it'll be complete.
- How wonderful
- Yes.
Ms. Higa, write your name.
Check out that signature!
Oh my gosh!
That's so cool!
Everyone from Okinawa is so lovely.
Okinawan grandpas and grandmas are cool.
MA-CHAN FROM BUNAGAYA
A-SA KOMACHI
AZAMA
HARU-CHAN
EMIKO - KAZUO
Oh, Rinrin looks like
she's having mixed feelings.
Oh, wow.
It's different from the daytime.
Kamaken is really stupid.
- Yeah.
- It's so lame.
He's a 30-year-old grown man.
What an idiot.
But, well, it's the last day.
He might've just said what
he thought at the beginning, you know.
Anyway, you never know until
you hear what the other party has to say.
His brain is rotten.
I mean, what else do you call it?
You know, I don't care
about kissing or cuddling.
- Uh-huh.
- Right?
I mean, you should wait
until you've sorted out your feelings
before you do that.
If he doesn't feel that way,
I'm backing off.
I mean, if you keep pursuing
that kind of guy,
do you think you can be happy? Really?
- I agree.
- That's why I'm so pissed off.
Hmm.
So, when it comes to
the graduation ceremony…
Uh-huh.
…if he confesses his feelings to you,
what would you say?
I'm starting to lose interest.
Wait.
So, it's already over?
Hmm, I guess it is.
I don't like guys who bounce between girls
before even dating.
- It's a big turn-off.
- Uh-huh.
Even if we started dating, he'd probably
chase any girl who messaged him.
Uh-huh.
But this isn't something you can solve
by getting mad on your own.
Mmm.
I'm so tired.
Even if Kamaken changes his attitude,
you've made up your mind,
you still don't want to date him?
I don't think so.
- I'm thinking of dropping out.
- You can't do that.
- I don't care anymore.
- That's not the answer.
- That's not it.
- I hear what you're saying but…
Look, I also wanted to graduate
with everyone.
But I think it's okay to drop out.
I can't do this.
- I totally get why you feel this way.
- I'm so tired.
I get it, I really do.
- But that would be so sad.
- It's okay. I'm tired.
So, are you okay with this weird feeling
being the last thing?
Yeah, it's fine.
That's sad.
- I'm so tired, I just--
- That's sad.
- Can I go now?
- No. Just let me finish my smoke.
- Enough.
- Sit down a second. Sit.
- No, I'm going now.
- Listen to what I have to say.
- I listened to you, so listen to me.
- What is it?
So, sit down, now.
- Sit down now.
- What is it? What?
Tell me why you want to drop out.
Well, I'm tired.
Why? You know why. I'm tired.
Look…
Go talk to him one last time.
- I don't need to talk to him.
- No, you can't run away like that.
- I'm going now. Bye.
- Wait-- At least think it through.
- Promise me you'll think about it.
- No, I've made up my mind.
Well, think about it again.
I told you, I've made
my decision. Thank you, Kahochi.
If you really thought about it,
you wouldn't drop out.
- Thank you.
- Hey.
Think about it. Just don't give in
too soon. I'm begging you.
No, I'm done.
Hey, what's wrong?
- He's a grown-up. He's stupid.
- Hey, wait.
I'm done.
What? I'm done.
Come on, don't be like that.
- Don't be like that.
- I'm done.
- What?
Hey. If you have something
to say, let's talk.
- I'm done. Leave me alone.
- Tell me.
We've been living together
this whole time.
We're friends. That means
we'll see this thing through together.
- Well, how should I put it?
- Mmm-hmm.
To be honest…
- I tried my best to get this far.
- Mmm.
- And I'm crushed again.
- Mmm-hmm.
I want to go home already.
I don't have anyone here anymore.
- Aw.
- Oh, what is happening?
- What?
- I know.
- Next episode's graduation?
- That's right.
- Yeah.
What is going on?
- And it's really ending this time?
- Yes.
- Next episode won't be four hours' long?
- No, it won't.
You promise?